import { v4 as uuidv4 } from "uuid";

export const ttfaq = [
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: "What is a professional fraternity?",
    answer: "A professional fraternity is a brotherhood consisting chiefly of individuals in a specific field of education, promoting professional development in addition to strengthening brotherly ties."
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: "Why Theta Tau?",
    answer: "Theta Tau is a diverse group of engineers who grow close together while striving towards similar goals. You will find our interests are wide and vary; some enjoy surfing on a nice afternoon, others may enjoy going to a concert on a weekend. All of us, however, are committed to helping one another become the best possible engineer and person they can be."
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: "How can I join Theta Tau?",
    answer: "You can become a part of Theta Tau by attending our rush week events and getting to know more about the Brothers and what the Fraternity stands for."
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: "Is there a minimum GPA requirement to become a member?",
    answer: "You must have be in good academic standing with the University (> 2.5 GPA). There are no exceptions to this rule. "
  }
  
  
];

export const rushfaq = [
  
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: "What is rush week?",
    answer: "Rush is a weeklong opportunity for you to learn more about Theta Tau by meeting both our active and graduated brothers. Rush consists of multiple events that will give you a taste of what the Fraternity stands for, whether you are a good fit for us, and whether we are a good fit for you. At the end of rush, we extend a limited number of interviews and bids. Those who receive bids can then decide whether or not they would like to accept their bids and continue with the process. Rushing is completely free of charge and there are no obligations."
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: "Who can come to rush?",
    answer: "While anyone is allowed to attend rush events, we only accept full-time students with majors in the UCSD Jacobs School of Engineering as well as Data Science and Math - Computer Science. There are no exceptions to this rule."
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: "Do I have to attend all rush events?",
    answer: "Although there is no formal requirement, we strongly encourage you to come out to as many events as you can. This gives us the chance to get to know you better and you the chance to get to know us."
  }
  
];

export const bidfaq = [
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: "What's a bid?",
    answer: "A bid is a formal invitation to begin the process of becoming a brother. You will be notified if you have been given a bid at the end of Rush."
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: "How do you choose who receives a bid?",
    answer: "Theta Tau searches for engineers who have a strong foundation in its three pillars: Brotherhood, Professionalism, and Philanthropy. We review each applicant as a whole (grades, personality, professionalism, resume, etc.) to determine whether we are the right fit for you."  
  },
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: "What is the time commitment after receiving a bid?",
    answer: "Prospective members can expect a workload similar to a 6-unit upper division engineering course. The process is led by senior members of the Fraternity, who assist prospective members in developing professional skills, aiding the community, and most important of all, getting to know their future brothers."  
  },
];
